### **Dayoung Kim**

### Jr. Front-end Web Developer

Address	Gyeongsangdo, South Korea
Mobile	+82 10 2869 7886
Email	kimdayoung771 @gmail.com
LinkedIn	https://www.linkedin.c om/in/dayoung-clara- kim/
Github	https://github.com/Day oung3460
Portfolio	https://dayoungportfoli o.netlify.app

#### PERSONAL SUMMARY

Junior Front-End Developer experiencing in a company that develops and services a blockchain-based platform. Skilledin developing and testing multiple web-based applications. Gained skills in aligning designs with clientrequirements and experience in resolving conflicts with colleagues professionally. Specializes in vanilla JavaScript and vue.js framework. Willing to learn native mobile development.

#### **EDUCATION**

programming academy, Deagu,

#### KEY SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS / Bootstrap
- JavaScript / jQuery
- Vue.js
- React.js
- Git(Github, Gitlab)
- TypeScript
- Kotlin
- JetBrains, Webstorm

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## Coinvest – Gyeongsan-si, South Korea Junior Front-end web developer

: Nov 2020 ~ Present

- Worked with a design team to resolve CSS issues.
- Design pages and components
- Turn design pages and components into vue.js
- Worked with back-end team collaboratively to make API specification

# UBIT and BES, Cryptocurrency Exchange Website (Jun 2021 ~ Present)

- Managing cryptocurrency exchange website development projects from initial design
- Using vue.js framework, Rest API(axios) and Web Socket
- Received real-time transaction data and drew a graph using Trading View chart library
- P2P exchange
- Library used:
  - grcode for OTP login
  - big-js to calculate big decimal
  - vue-i18n for translation
  - vue-router
  - vue-socket.io
  - vuex

### Jangboda, a traditional market delivery application (Nov 2020 ~ May 2021)

- Developed and maintained webview for hybrid application.
- Using vue.js framework and Rest API(axios)
- Using Kakao map open API
- Using NICE open API for user authentication
- The monthly active users was recorded average 500.